<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="permission_message" translatable="false">This app needs to record audio and recognize your speech.</string>
    <string name="listening" translatable="false">Listening…</string>
    <string name="load_file" translatable="false">Load file</string>

    <string name="background" translatable="false">Glasgow Caledonian University was established in 1993 as a result of a merger between the Queen"'"s College, and Glasgow Polytechnic and since then has become one of the largest universities in Scotland with nearly 17,000 students. The campus is self–contained and situated right in the heart of the lively city of Glasgow. The University is made up of three academic schools - School of Health and Life Sciences, Glasgow School for Business and Society, and School of Computing, Engineering and Built Environment. Glasgow Caledonian is also home to the Glasgow School for Business and Society, the largest business school in Scotland. Each school contains state-of-the-art laboratories and a number of renowned centres of excellence. The university"'"s current chancellor is Annie Lennox and the current principal and vice chancellor is Pamela Gillies. With campuses stretching across the globe in London and New York, the main campus is based in the heart of Glasgow in Cowcadden"'"s Road.</string>
    <string name="department_info" translatable="false"> Glasgow Caledonian University has three different schools on its main campus: "\n"The School of Computing, Engineering and Built Environment, the School for Business and Society and the School of Health and Life Sciences. \n Computing Engineering and Built Enviornment: \n This School has over 200 academic staff in its eight departments. Our primary output, consistent with the University’s strategy, is the education of students to the highest possible standard, producing highly qualified graduates with degrees that are accredited by the premier national and international authorities. \n School for Business and Society: \n This school covers such a wide span that the schools departments is split into three areas: \n Law, Economics, Accountancy and Risk \n Business Management \n Social Sciences, Media and Journalism \n School of Health and Life Sciences: \n The strengths of the School of Health and Life Sciences and the associated Institute of Applied Health Research lie in our professional expertise, multidisciplinary team-based service delivery, and strict adherence to regulatory standards that require partnerships with the public, and commercial and non-governmental organisations. The school offers a breadth of theoretical knowledge, practice skills and educational engagement spanning community to bench to business and bedside, and back into community, and supported by ongoing investment in our people and facilities. The school consists of eight departments. </string>
    <string name="CEBELink" translatable="false"><a href="https://www.gcu.ac.uk/cebe/aboutus/welcome/">For more information on the CEBE</a></string>
    <string name="BusinessLink" translatable="false"><a href="https://www.gcu.ac.uk/gsbs/">For more information on the School of Business and Society</a></string>
    <string name="HealthLink" translatable="false"><a href="https://www.gcu.ac.uk/hls/">For more information on the School of Health and Life Sciences</a></string>
    <string name="buildings" translatable="false">There are many different buildings which exist in the main campus of Glasgow Caledonian University. For academic sessions, for example lectures, seminars, and tutorials. The George Moore Building, the Govan Mbeki Building, and the Hamish Wood buildings are used. In the George Moore building, there is also the University resteraunt, and Campus Life desk. The library is located in the Saltire Centre, in between the Hamish Wood and the George Moore building. Connected to the George Moore Building is the Charles Oakley building which holds laboratories for Science students. For any other recreation or for the 24 7 computer labs, the Students Association is available for use. Glasgow Caledonian also includes a gym facility called the Arc which is based at the entrance of the campus opposite the Buchanan Bus Station. For University Offices, there is the William Harley building which was formerly the main site for the library. Other offices are found in the Britannia Building, based next to the William Harley building. The campus is also host to a Nursery for student parents, as well as student accommodation based in the Caledonian Court. </string>
    <string name="library" translatable="false">Our award winning library, the Saltire Centre, gives access to more than 270,000 books, 350 open access PCs and a huge range of online resources including databases, ebooks, journals and more. \n It is open 7 days a week, with support available from staff at The Library Desk. You can also contact your librarian who can help you make the best use of our resources. \n Your student card is your library card and you are automatically a member of the library when you register. Please note it can take 24 to 48 hours before your details are transferred to the library system. Only after this time will you be able to borrow from the library.\n The library offers a variety of study spaces so that you can choose a place that best suits your needs, be it social and group study on the lower levels or individual and silent study on the upper levels. \n The library is also home to the Archives and Special Collections, which hold rare and unique items from GCU"'"s past together with other collections of national importance. \n \n The library"'"s opening times are as follows: \n Monday to Friday:\n Building: 7AM to 11PM \n Desk: 9AM to 8AM \n \n Weekends: \n Building: 9AM to 6PM \n Desk:10AM to 6PM \n</string>
    <string name="liblink" translatable="false"><a href="https://www.gcu.ac.uk/study/internationalstudents/facilitiessupport/thesaltirecentre/"> For more info on the Saltire Centre </a></string>
    <string name="contact" translatable="false">Contact Info: \n \n Glasgow Caledonian University \n Cowcaddens Road \n Glasgow \n G4 0BA \n Scotland, UK \n \n 0141 331 3000 \n "\n"Study Enquiries: "\n"Our Student Enquiries Team are happy to help with enquiries on any of the following: \n \n - How to Apply \n - Programme Entry Requirements \n - International Students Enquiries \n - Scholarship/Fees Information \n \n 01413318630</string>

</resources>
